M: So Ben, what do you do?
B: I’m a student.
M: Nice.
What do you study?
I: He studies photography.
His photos are amazing!
M: Cool.
Maybe you can work for us in a few years.
B: Yeah, maybe.
I: Ben’s very artistic.
M: Artistic? That’s great.
Do you have a real job?
B: A real job?
M: Yeah.
Do you have a job with a salary?
B: Yeah.
Um… Well, I work at a café.
M: Perfect.
If you can’t earn enough money as a photographer, people always need coffee.
B: Yeah.
I guess you’re right.
W: Here you are.
Sorry about the mistake.
M: Oh, don’t worry Ben, I’ve got this.
E: How was your evening?
B: I didn’t enjoy it much.
E: Are you still out with them?
B: No, they all went to have a drink.
I didn’t want to go, so I said I was tired… I really don’t like these people.
They’re too… confident for me.
E: There’s nothing wrong with being confident, Ben.
B: Well, they’re just a bit fake, that’s all.
E: Did Izzy go with them?
B: Yeah.
E: She likes these people, right?
She does.
She’s… changing.
E: Things change, Ben, and people change too.
That’s life.